autoshowny.com 2019-06-10

# Privacy - New York International Auto Show

This website is owned and operated by the New York International Auto (“NYIAS”, **“we”, “us”, “our”** ) which is owned by the Greater New York Automobile Dealers Association, Inc. This policy provides you with details on the information collected from you and the uses we may make of your personal information. This policy may be updated as technology changes or the law requires, so please check back periodically. If you continue to visit this website and use the services made available to you after such changes, you hereby acknowledge, agree to, and provide your consent to the changes.

We encourage you to read this policy to learn more about what information we collect, how we use it, and how you can opt-in or opt-out of receiving communications from us. Additionally, this policy includes information about how we endeavor to protect your data. If you have any questions about our collection and use of your information, please contact us at [assistance@gnyada.com.](mailto:assistance@gnyada.com.)

### Information We Collect

We may collect two types of information about you when you visit our websites, contact us with questions: (1) personally identifiable information (such as your name, address, telephone number, e-mail address), and (2) nonpersonal, aggregate information (such as information regarding the pages on our site you have visited).

### Personally Identifiable Information

The only personally identifiable information that NYIAS collects and stores is the information that you have chosen to provide through optional, voluntary submissions. We may collect personal identification information in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when users visit our site, click on various links on the site, register on the site, place an order, subscribe to an electronic communication, contact NYIAS via an email address provided in a hyperlink, respond to a survey, fill out a form, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site or through communications

NYIAS uses the personally identifiable information primarily for the following purposes:

  * To process a request made by you to receive our electronic newsletters;
  * To participate in our message boards or forums;
  * To permit participation in polls and surveys;
  * To complete any other transaction or service requested by you.
  * To unaffiliated third-party service providers, agents or independent contractors who help us maintain our websites and provide other administrative services.
  * To notify you about a material change to this Privacy Policy or the Terms of Use, if necessary.
  * To comply with the law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to conform to the requirements of law or comply with legal process served on us, protect and defend our rights or property, including the rights and property of NYIAS or act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of our end users.
  * To track and analyze nonidentifying and aggregate usage and volume statistical information from our visitors and customers and provide such information to third parties.
  * In the event of a corporate restructuring (such as, a sale, merger or other asset transfer), we may share your Personal Information with a third party.
  * If NYIAS collects your personally identifiable information for one of the purposes described above, it may store such information on its servers or in one (or more) of its databases. If you do not want NYIAS to use and store your information in accordance with this policy, please do not submit any personally identifiable information to NYIAS.

Except as described in this Privacy Policy or at the time we request the information, we do not sell or rent personal identification information to others.  We may use third party service providers to help us operate our business, this site or administer activities on our behalf, such as distribution of newsletters or surveys. We may share your information with these third parties for those limited purposes provided that you have given us your permission.

### Providing Personal Data to Others

We may disclose your personal data relating to transactions with the New York International Automobile Show to our executives, financial services, insurers, affiliated companies, professional advisors. Except as specified in our Privacy Policy, New York International Auto Show does not divulge any personal data information about an individual user to a third party.

### Non-personally Identifiable Information

NYIAS also collects non-personally identifiable information about your visit to our websites. This information is aggregated and cannot be used to identify you personally.  We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.

Information New York International Auto Show gathers through aggregated tracking information derived mainly by tallying page views throughout our sites: This information allows us to better tailor our content to readers’ needs and to help our advertisers and sponsors better understand the demographics of our audience. Because New York International Auto Show derives revenue from sponsorships and advertising, providing such aggregated demographic data is essential to keeping our service free to users.

NYIAS uses your non-personally identifiable information to manage its websites. NYIAS may analyze the data about visits to the websites to make them more accessible and interesting. NYIAS may share that data with third parties, usually to provide services for NYIAS associated with the maintenance of the websites.

### How NYIAS Uses Optional Voluntary Information

We offer the following free services, which require some type of voluntary submission of personal information by users:

  1. Electronic newsletters policy (Dispatches)

We will offer a free electronic newsletter to users. NYIAS gathers the email addresses of users who voluntarily subscribe. Users may remove themselves from this mailing list by following the link provided in every newsletter that points users to the subscription management page. Users can also subscribe to the newsletters at the time of registration.

  2. Virtual Garage/Forums policy

Users of the site’s Virtual Garage and Forums must register separately for these services (both are free of charge) in order to post messages. During registration the user is required to supply a username, password, and email address.

  4. Polling

We may offer interactive polls to users so they can easily share their opinions with other users and see what our audience thinks about important issues. Opinions or other responses to polls are aggregated and are not identifiable to any particular user. NYIAS may use a system to “tag” users after they have voted, so they can vote only once on a particular question. This tag is not correlated with information about individual users.

  5. Surveys

NYIAS may occasionally conduct user surveys to better target our content to our audience. We sometimes share the aggregated demographic information in these surveys with our sponsors, advertisers and partners. We never share any of this information about specific individuals with any third party.

### Usage tracking

NYIAS tracks user traffic patterns throughout all of our sites. However, we do not correlate this information with data about individual users. NYIAS does break down overall usage statistics according to a user’s domain name, browser type, and MIME type by reading this information from the browser string (information contained in every user’s browser).

NYIAS may track and catalog the search terms that users enter in our Search function, but this tracking is never associated with individual users. We use tracking information to determine which areas of our sites users like and don’t like based on traffic to those areas. We do not track what individual users read, but rather how well each page performs overall. This helps us continue to build a better service for you.

### Cookies and Similar Technologies

This website uses “cookies.”  A “cookie” is a file containing a string of letters or numbers sent to your browser from a web server and stored by your computer. Generally, cookies are used to enable us to deliver better and more personalized service, assist us in tracking visits to the website, and to measure visitor patterns. This information is not personally identifiable and is used by us only to improve the website. We do not use cookies to retrieve personal information from your computer, to retrieve other information from your computer for purposes that are unrelated to the website or your interaction with the website. We reserve the right to disclose or utilize any of this information in aggregate form, for any purpose, at our sole discretion. By modifying your browser preferences, you can accept or reject any or all cookies. If you choose to reject all cookies, you will not be able to access the portions of the website that require you to register in order to participate.

You may have certain rights under the Communications Act, Federal Trade Commission Act, and other state. federal, and international statutes such as CASL and GDPR that may also apply.

### OPT OUT Policy

If you have subscribed to or are otherwise receiving NYIAS Overdrive news, alerts, blog posts, or similar information from us by email and no longer want to receive such information in the future, you may opt-out of receiving these emails by clicking the “unsubscribe” link at the bottom of those emails you receive. Please allow ample time for us to process your request. If you are having difficulty unsubscribing, please contact us using the Contact Us page or at [info@autoshowny.com](mailto:info@autoshowny.com)

Please note that even if you opt-out of receiving emails, you may still receive communications related to your interaction with us (such as confirmation of a registration or form submission) or otherwise as required by law. Also note that we may need to keep personal information we have collected about you to respect your decision to opt-out, for record-keeping, research and other purposes.

### Third-Party Websites

Websites to which we provide links may have different policies relating to your privacy and information they collect about you. Visitors should consult other sites’ privacy policies, as we may not have control over information that is submitted to, or controlled by, third parties.

### International Transfer of Information

If you choose to provide us with personally identifiable information, it may be stored in the United States and in other jurisdictions. If you are visiting our websites from the European Union or other regions with laws governing data collection and use, please note that your personally identifiable information may be transferred to the United States, and to other jurisdictions, which may not have the same data protection laws as the European Union and may not afford many of the rights conferred upon data subjects in the European Union. You acknowledge that you understand: (i) your personally identifiable information may be used for the uses identified above in accordance with this Privacy Policy; and (ii) your personally identifiable information may be transferred to the United States, or other jurisdictions as indicated above.  However, transfers of personally identifiable information by European citizens will be protected by appropriate safeguards regulated by our European Commission, the General Data Protection Regulations (GDPR) of the European Union.

### Changes to this Privacy Policy

NYIAS reserves the right to change or update this privacy policy from time to time by publishing a new version on our website [info@autoshowny.com](mailto:info@autoshowny.com).  You should check this page occasionally to insure you are happy with any changes to the policy.  When we do, we will also revise the “Last Updated” date at the bottom of this privacy policy.

### Security

We are committed to using all commercially reasonable efforts to maintaining the security of your Personal Information. We adopt appropriate data collection, storage, and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our site. Sensitive and private data exchange between the site and its users happens over a SSL secured communication channel and is encrypted and protected with digital signatures. However, you should keep in mind that our sites are run on software, hardware, and networks, any component of which may, from time to time, require maintenance or experience problems or breaches of security beyond our control. While we take steps to protect your personal information and keep it secure, you also play a role in protecting your information. You must maintain the security of your online transactions by not sharing your passwords and account information with any unauthorized parties. Please also be aware that despite our best intentions and the guidelines outlined in this privacy policy, no data transmission over the Internet or encryption method can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. We cannot guarantee the security of any information you transmit to us or from our sites, and therefore you use our Sites at your own risk.

This website contains links to other websites for the purchase of third party products and services. Please be aware that we are not responsible for such third-party sites in any manner including without limitation, the privacy practices of other websites. We encourage you to be aware when you access any such third-party links and to read the privacy policies of each website that you access. This Privacy Policy only applies to information collected by us by this website.

### Data Retention

We will keep your personal information for no longer than is necessary to perform the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy. Laws may require us to hold certain information for specific periods.

### Individual Rights of European Union Residents

For residents of the European Union only. Under European data protection law, in certain circumstances, you have the right to:

  * Request access to any personal information we hold about you (“Subject Access Request”) as well as related information, including the purposes for processing the personal information, the recipients or categories of recipients with whom the personal information has been shared, where possible, the period for which the personal information will be stored, the source of the personal information, and the existence of any automated decision making;
  * Obtain without undue delay the rectification of any inaccurate personal information we hold about you;
  * Request that personal information held about you is deleted;
  * Prevent or restrict processing of your personal information; and
  * Request transfer of personal information directly to a third party where this is technically feasible.

Also, where you believe that we have not complied with its obligation under this privacy policy or European law, you have the right to make a complaint to an EU Data Protection Authority, such as the UK Information Commissioner’s Office”.

You can exercise any of these rights by contacting us using the Contact Us page or at [info@autoshowny.com](mailto:info@autoshowny.com).

We will store your personal information, in a form which permits us to identify you, for no longer than is necessary for the purpose for which the personal information is processed. These rights may be limited in some situations, for example, where we can demonstrate that we have a legal requirement to process your information. In some instances, this may mean that we are able to retain your information even if you withdraw your consent.  We may retain and use your personal information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements and rights, or if it is not technically reasonably feasible to remove it.  Consistent with these requirements, we will try to delete your personal information quickly upon your request.  We hope we can satisfy any queries you may have about the way we process your data. If you have any concerns about how we process your data or would like to opt-out of receiving marketing communications, please contact us at [info@autoshowny.com](mailto:info@autoshowny.com)

You have the right to confirmation as to whether or not we process your personal data and, where we do, access to the personal data, together with certain additional information.   That additional information includes details of the purposes of the processing, the categories of personal data concerned and the recipients of the personal data. Providing the rights and freedoms of others are not affected, we will supply to you a copy of your personal data. The first copy will be provided free of charge, but additional copies may be subject to a reasonable fee.

For residents of the European Union, in the event you have unresolved concerns, you also have the right to complain to a data protection authority.

### Special Policy Regarding Information from Minors

We do not knowingly collect, use or disclose personal information from children under the age of 13 or target our site or services to children under 13.

### Choice of Law and Forum

This Privacy Policy and our legal obligations hereunder are subject to the laws of New York, U.S.A., regardless of your location. You hereby consent to the exclusive jurisdiction of and venue in the federal and state courts located in New York County, New York, U.S.A. in all disputes arising out of or relating to the Services.

### Contact

If you have any questions or comments regarding our Privacy Policy or our sites, please contact us using the Contact Us page or at [info@autoshowny.com](mailto:info@autoshowny.com).

You can also write to us at:

Greater New York Automobile Dealers Association, Inc.  
18-10 Whitestone Expressway  
Whitestone, NY 11357USA  
Att: NYIAS Show Director

Last Updated: February 14, 2019
